Vishal Sir, look at ICICI Lombard,
Lombard
[Music]
and the man has a
very big
weakness, avoid it
if it is in your hand and the exit
decision can also be taken here, even
if I have a position of Rs. 1400, then
I will say here, exit here once
and if the stock
starts suspending above 20% of that, if it starts
suspending above this 100160, then
you should buy it, otherwise you should buy
this stock probably below this, I am not wrong,
which is suggesting me the weekly chart,
first of all its major support is 1068,
if 1068 is broken then
buying should be done, if it breaks below
₹910
[Music] then it should be bought,
according to me it will
go above 1068, above 1060, above 1160,
here you can tell me